Privacy Policy
==============

Updated 13 November 2019

### Introduction

Vivi is dedicated to safeguarding your privacy and upholding the highest data protection standards. This privacy policy details the personal information we collect, our usage practices, disclosure parameters, and your rights concerning your data.

### Data Usage

We categorize data as either user data or customer data, both of which may include personal information. User data pertains to individuals using our products and services, while customer data relates to entities purchasing them.

All data collected is utilized solely for service provision, user communication, and as legally required. This includes service operation, maintenance, enhancement, user authentication, and addressing administrative, security, and legal matters.

### Collecting Data

Vivi collects both Personally Identifiable Information (PII) and non-Personally Identifiable Information (non-PII) to provide and improve our services. The specific types of PII we gather include:

* First Name and Surname
* Email Address
* Device Type and Operating System Version

This personal information is collected when you communicate with us, register as a user, engage with our product, interact with our website, or submit an inquiry. We also obtain data from your Single Sign-On (SSO) provider and maintain sales and marketing details within our Customer Relationship Management (CRM) system.

We collect and store data from business inquiries and potential leads in our CRM, including email, phone number, job position, organization, and country to engage and tailor our approach with prospective customers.

We also use website cookies which are used enhance user experience. You can manage your preferences regarding cookies via your browser settings which could affect the functionality of our site.

In addition to our own cookies, we use Google Analytics and Google AdWords to analyze site usage and deliver targeted advertisements, respectively. Google anonymously collects information using cookies including but not limited to age, gender, and geographic location.

In terms of non-PII, we collect:

* Media content that you upload to Vivi Central, which may include images, videos, and other types of files.
* Usage information, which helps us understand how you use our product, providing metrics for product performance and user engagement.

This comprehensive data collection enables us to tailor our services to your needs, enhance product functionality, and ensure a seamless user experience.

For a detailed list of third-party service providers that assist us in delivering our services, please refer to [our list of sub processors](https://www.vivi.io/privacy-policy/sub-processors/).

### Data Security

Vivi implements stringent security measures to protect your data, utilizing Amazon Web Services (AWS) for secure cloud-based data management. We ensure the safeguarding of your information, significantly minimizing the risk of unauthorized physical access by not retaining any customer data on-premises.

Access to your account is facilitated through a password and/or a unique username chosen by you or through your SSO provider if you have this configured, with the encryption of passwords further bolstering security.

All data is encrypted during transmission and while stored. Vivi recognizes that despite these precautions, no method of data transmission or storage over the Internet or via wireless networks can be guaranteed as entirely secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information you must be aware that:

* There are privacy and security limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control.
* We cannot guarantee the security, integrity, and privacy of any information and data exchanged between you and our website.
* We are not responsible for any loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure or alteration of your information by third parties who may intercept or access the data in transit.

In the unlikely event of a data breach, Vivi is fully committed to complying with the requirements of all relevant Privacy Laws and the provisions of the GDPR, where applicable.

Should you suspect any unauthorized use of your account or a breach of security, we ask that you to inform us without delay.

### Data Retention

Data you provide, and we collect, including personal information, is retained as long as necessary to deliver services to you, or until you instruct us to erase your data. Specific retention periods for different data types are determined by operational necessity and compliance with legal and regulatory standards.

### Access to Personal Information

You maintain the right to access your personal data that we hold. Upon request, Vivi will provide you with a copy of your personal data. If you so choose, you may also request the deletion of your personal data from our systems, ensuring your right to be forgotten.

In line with data protection regulations, Vivi may disclose your personal data for specific purposes:

* Responding to lawful requests for information from courts, government agencies, or legal representatives;
* Conducting investigations into suspected fraud or unlawful activities, ensuring the integrity of our services;
* Protecting our legal rights and interests in scenarios such as disputes or legal proceedings; and
* Facilitating the transfer of data as part of due diligence or completion of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, or similar event.

Vivi is committed to handling all personal data in accordance with the legal standards and privacy obligations that govern our operations. Your ability to access, port, and erase your data is a testament to our commitment to upholding your privacy rights.

### Disclosing Data

Data may be disclosed under lawful circumstances such as court orders, government requests or during corporate transactions. We also disclose data to address fraud, protect our lawful interests and in connection with the sale or purchase of business entities.

### Overseas Data Transfers

We maintain all product data within Australia and do not engage in data transfers outside of our operational region.

### Third-party Interactions

Our data interactions with third parties are limited to specific purposes:

* Google Analytics/AdWords: For marketing and analytics purposes on our marketing website.
* HubSpot: For CRM and customer account management.
* Amazon Web Services: For hosting the Vivi platform.
* Microsoft: For various business operations.
* Atlassian: For customer support activities.

### Protection of Children's Personal Information

Vivi does not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 13. We adhere to FERPA regulations, requiring school consent for student data collection, which is used exclusively for educational benefits.

No data sharing occurs beyond these interactions, except for data processed by AskNicely for customer experience measurement purposes.

### Complaint Procedures

Concerns regarding privacy practices can be addressed by emailing [privacy@vivi.io](mailto:privacy@vivi.io) or by contacting your Customer Success Manager if you are an existing customer. We are committed to promptly investigating and resolving complaints in compliance with privacy regulations.

### Opt-out Mechanisms

To unsubscribe from marketing communications, please utilize the unsubscribe feature in our emails. For other data preferences, contact us at [privacy@vivi.io](mailto:privacy@vivi.io) or if you are an existing customer, your Customer Success Manager.

### Updates

We will notify customers via email of any significant updates to our privacy policy.

### Contact

For all privacy-related inquiries or concerns, please reach out to us at the dedicated email address: [privacy@vivi.io](mailto:privacy@vivi.io).

##### Join our mailing list

For monthly classroom technology resources.

##### Follow us

* [
    
    ](https://www.facebook.com/vivieducation)
* [
    
    ](http://www.twitter.com/vivieducation)
* [
    
    ](https://www.linkedin.com/company/vivieducation/)
* [
    
    ](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQbZJeWGyP4LeSmy0elootg)

© 2024 Vivi International Pty Ltd
